>> DEMOCRATS CONTINUING TO CARRY
ON FOR A DEAD X TRAFFICKER,
JEFFREY EPSTEIN, IS BEING
PROTECTED, JUST RUNNING OUT OF
TIME.
AND WE ASKED HIS OFFICE WHY, AND
THEY SAID THE TIMING.
BUT HE WASN'T EVEN READY TO HOLD
A VOTE, HE WAS IN CHICAGO
CUTTING A RIBBON AT A BATTERY
PLANT.
THERE HE IS RIGHT THERE.
HE HAD DIRT ON A LOT OF POWERFUL
PEOPLE.
SECRETS THAT KEPT EVERYBODY IN
LINE, HE'S BEEN DEAD FOR FOUR
YEARS COME ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT
KEEPS BLOCKING THE CLIENT LIST.
JOINING ME NOW IS A
WHISTLEBLOWER AND FORMER CIA
OFFICER.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US, JOHN.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHY WE CANNOT
GET THE FLIGHT LOGS?
>> NO, THERE'S NO REASON WHY WE
CANNOT GET THEM.
I USED TO BE THESE SENIOR
INVESTIGATOR AND WE HAD
INVESTIGATIVE POWER, ALL IT
TAKES IS A SIGNATURE OF THE
SENATOR.
IT CAN BE GIVEN AT 2:00 O'CLOCK
IN THE MORNING OR 8:00 O'CLOCK
IN THE MORNING OR WHENEVER YOU
WANT US TO SIT DOWN AND SIGN THE
PAPER.
SO THIS NOTION THAT THEY RAN OUT
OF TIME IS NOT SENSIBLE.
>> THEY WON'T BE ABLE TO USE
THAT EXCUSE FOREVER.
THERE'S GOT TO BE TIME AND ALL
THEY NEED IS A JOHN HANCOCK TO
GET A SUBPOENA.
SO THEY CAN'T CONTINUE TO COME
UP WITH THESE BS EXCUSES BECAUSE
THEY WILL CONTINUE TO LOOK AS
COMPLICIT AS POSSIBLE.
>> YES, THAT'S RIGHT, AND THEY
ARE IF THEY INSIST UPON THIS
NONSENSICAL POLICY.
YOU KNOW, HE'S DEAD?
HE IS DEAD AND HE HAS BEEN DEAD
FOR FOUR YEARS, HE IS A
CONVICTED PEDOPHILE, A CONVICTED
CHILD MOLESTER.
WHAT POSSIBLE REASON COULD THERE
BE TO HIDE THIS INFORMATION.
HOW COULD THIS NOT BE IN THE
PUBLIC INTEREST?
IT IS ALMOST A JOKE WHEN YOU
THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE THE CONSTITUENTS
ARE DEMANDING THAT THIS
INFORMATION BE KEPT SECRET.
>> HIS CONSTITUENTS ARE LIKE
OKAY, CAN YOU GET THE MIGRANTS
OUT OF CHICAGO, PLEASE?
THEY ARE NOT SAYING BLOCK THE
LINES.
>> THERE IS NO REASON WHATSOEVER
TO KEEP THIS INFORMATION SECRET.
IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS THAT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE HAVE THE RIGHT
TO KNOW, THEY OWN THIS
INFORMATION AND THEY HAVE A
RIGHT TO ITS RELEASE.
>> IF YOU ARE ON THE PLANE WITH
JEFFREY EPSTEIN, MAYBE YOU WERE
INNOCENT AND DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> JUST LIKE BOB KENNEDY, HE
EXPLAINED HIMSELF VERY WELL, HE
SAID I WAS ON THE PLANE WITH MY
WIFE AND WITH ALL MY KIDS.
WE WERE ON OUR WAY FOR EASTER TO
PALM BEACH.
AND MAXWELL OFFERED US A LIFT.
>> I'M SURE THAT EVERYBODY HAS A
PERFECTLY REASONABLE EXPLANATI